kannadamatrimony.com 2016-04-05

# www.kannadamatrimony.com

Since we are strongly committed to your right to privacy, we have drawn out a privacy statement with regard to the information we collect from you. You acknowledge that you are disclosing information voluntarily. By using the website and/or by providing your information, you consent to the collection and use of the info you disclose on the website in accordance with this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree for use of your information, please do not use or access this website.

We use a secure server for credit card transactions to protect the credit card information of our users and Cookies are used to store the login information. Cookies are small files placed on your hard drive that will assist us in providing our services. You may also encounter Cookies or identical/related devices on certain pages of the website that are placed by third parties. We do not control the use of cookies by third parties.

What information you need to give in to use this site?

The information we gather from members and visitors who apply for the various services our site offers includes, but may not be limited to, email address, first name, last name, date of birth, educational qualifications a user-specified password, mailing address, zip/pin code and telephone/mobile number or fax number.

If you establish a credit account with us to pay the fees we charge, some additional information, including a billing address, a credit/debit card number and a credit/debit card expiration date and tracking information from cheques or demand drafts is collected.

How the site uses the information it collects/tracks?

 **CONSIM** collects information from our users primarily to ensure that we are able to fulfill your requirements and to deliver Personalised experience.

With whom the site shares the information it collects/tracks?

**CONSIM** does not sell, rent, or loan any identifiable information at the individual level regarding its customers to any third party. However, we may share such identifiable information with our associates/affiliates/subsidiaries and such associates/affiliates/subsidiaries may market to you as a result of such sharing. Any information you give us is held with the utmost care and security. We are also bound to cooperate fully should a situation arise where we are required by law or legal process to provide information about a customer/visitor

Our Website links to other websites that may collect personally identifiable information about you. We are not responsible for the privacy policy or the contents of those linked websites.

Do all visitors have to pay?

NO. All visitors to our site may browse the site, search the ads and view any articles or features our site has to offer without entering any personal information or paying money.

How to unsubscribe the membership?

The members are requested to login to the relevant pages for unsubscription.

Can users contact any number of profiles in a single day?

As a paid member of this site, you have the privilege to contact hundreds of profiles. However, there is a specified limit to send 100 messages per day due to fair online usage policy.

Change of Privacy Policy

We may change this Privacy Policy without notice from time to time based on your comments or as a result of a change of policy in our company.

Demographic Data

Demographic data is also collected at our site. Demographic data is used to go with our visitors’ experience at our site, showing them content that we think they might be interested in, and their preferred content. We may disclose some data with advertisers on a non-personally identifiable basis.

Mobile Device

If accessing of our website of any applications is downloaded by your mobile , we may collect your mobile device information, operating system and version information, and IP address.

Disclosure By Law

You acknowledge and agree that we may disclose information you provide if required to do so by law, at the request of a third party, or if we, in our sole discretion, believe that disclosure is reasonable to (1) comply with the law, requests or orders from law enforcement, or any legal process 

Disclosure to Protect Abuse Victims

We reserve the right, but have no obligation, to disclose any information that you submit to us if in our sole opinion, we suspect or have reason to suspect, that the information involves a party who may be the victim of abuse in any form. We may disclose Information to concerned authorities that we, in our sole discretion, deem appropriate to handle such disclosure. . You hereby acknowledge and agree that we are permitted to make such disclosure. This clause over-rides any of the provisions of our terms and conditions and privacy policy.

How to contact us

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us by email or postal mail as follows: 

Privacy Officer

Address: Consim USA Inc. 220, Davidson Avenue ,  
Suite 315, Somerset , New Jersey USA  
privacy@consimusa.com
